Hello, everyone!
The livestreaming of J Weekly
and the Rehab Club's
charity fundraising Static Apnea Challenge
will now begin.
Without further ado,
Jarvis is ready to inhale pure oxygen,
the Static Apnea Challenge will soon begin.
(Three months after the incident)
Jarvis...
Get up! Enough horsing around...
Get up, Jarvis...
Hey, are you OK?
Gogo Sir...still looking at the case
from three months ago?
I still can't figure it out.
Relax! It's lunchtime. Let's go eat.
Are you OK, Wu Sir?
What are you laughing at?
This clip is hilarious...
(Neighbor Vs stink bomb)
It's me again, Agent J.
Today's game is very simple.
We have two gas cylinders.
Pick one and take a whiff.
One is oxygen.
The other is...more than that.
Agent J Channel?
What did you give me? It stinks!
Relax! It's just a stink bomb.
J Weekly had a Static Apnea Challenge before
they meant to use one of these
to trick one of their own.
Hold on. Rewind that.
I want to listen again.
J Weekly had an Static Apnea
Challenge before
they meant to use one of these
to trick one of their own.
That's it!
Using the stink bomb on their own staff
was never disclosed to the public.
What does that mean?
It means this Agent J
is connected to the livestreaming of the
Static Apnea Challenge three months ago.
What other clips does he have?
Who's the moderator?
They never show their faces.
What about the Static Apnea Challenge?
Three months ago, I was at an exchange
with the Mainland Police.
I missed it.
The case was connected to J Weekly.
Three months ago, all their videos
were about pulling pranks on people.
What's going on?
Yeah!
Keep it up...
Please take off your jacket.
Sorry! This is a routine check.
I'm in a hurry!
Run, Tom! Run!
Hurry...run!
The J Weekly Channel,
was quite a hit a year ago.
It went viral after Wendy showed up.
(Little J Media)
Who are you?
I'm Wendy, your diehard fan.
Jarvis, you're so amazing!
I've been following you for a long time.
Can we help you?
I want to join you.
Join us?
What are your strengths?
I'm pure and true.
More importantly, I really care
and I enjoy pulling pranks.
It's not as easy as you think.
You must use your head.
The case started with Wendy on a trampoline.
You have a dog and it went missing.
How can you find it?
Call the Police? Dial 999?
Wrong!
The answer is dye your hair blonde.
Because it's a golden retriever.
Go to Hell!
Are you OK?
I'm fine...I'd rather kill myself
than answer your dumb IQ questions.
(Three months ago)
Up...
Today, the Fake Metal Detector prank
reached 500K views!
Yeah!
It's not only in the top spot,
it also broke our channel record.
Yeah!
This "cup" is your award.
Mr. Tsang Chun-kit, the Fake Metal Detector
broke the 500K viewership,
how do you feel about that?
I would like to thank a fellow moron,
my partner in crime, Paul.
This moron is not only my co-host,
we were up all night brainstorming.
It was his idea.
He deserves this "cup" as well.
OK...
Hung Tzi-long, your partner thanked you.
Say something.
I also wish to thank this moron, Tom.
To be able to work with
such a talented moron,
the pleasure is all mine, moron!
Cheers!
Hey, don't drink from the bottle.
What about us?
You want to drink this?
Go ahead!
On this happy occasion, let's take a selfie.
Wait...don't forget our linchpin,
Auntie Ching.
Auntie Ching!
We won't be here without Auntie Ching.
Me? I'm just your cleaning lady.
Of course you can do without me.
But not without your sweet soup.
We'd be dead if we pull an all-nighter
without it.
There's more.
We'll never forget her special recipe...
...Braised chicken wings.
Say no more, let's take a picture.
Yes!
1...2...3...another one!
Go ahead, I'll go clean up.
OK!
Again.
Did you forget something?
You want to be in the center?
OK...come on!
Yes!
Jarvis, you're back!
Popping the champagne without me?
What are we celebrating?
Tom and Paul's Fake Metal Detector
just hit the 500K mark
and set a new record.
Not bad.
But only because you, the master of pranks
were leading them,
that's why they did so well.
You should get the credit.
Wendy is right.
Without you leading us
and giving our video the final touch,
we couldn't have done it.
Little J Media has a pool of talent.
Thanks to Tom and Paul,
who set a new record for us.
We also have our diehard fan Wendy,
and also Modem...and Peter.
As long as we stay united,
J Weekly will be Hong Kong's top channel.
Cheers...
Close the door!
Good job, 500K hits.
You popped the champagne without me.
Are you slighting me?
I forgot. Sorry!
Did you forget how you ended up here?
(Two years ago)
Hey!
Did you get the letter?
Yeah, we're now extras.
Are we that bad?
Even five shows a year can't put
food on the table.
Switching us to extras is like firing us.
Right!
This has a nice view.
Pick a spot and get ready to camp out here.
Good idea!
Gentlemen, do you have time...
Are you Tsang Chun-kit?
You know me?
Of course! You work at the TV station.
I see you on TV all the time.
He's quite good.
Nice to meet you.
Since you're not busy.
Let's play a game.
Here's $2,000.
If you win, the money is yours.
We hit rock bottom back then.
Thanks for bringing us on board
and giving us a chance as a host
so we can get some exposure.
And how to shoot, edit and brainstorm.
Didn't I teach you everything?
You made us what we are today.
When we first started the channel,
the three of us had to do everything.
We didn't mind the hard work and
charged ahead.
We went up the river and got us
where we are today.
You know why we're still here?
Because of what's here!
An online channel is not just
about viewership.
You must know what kind of content
will prompt viewers to top up.
The key is the money goes
directly to the channel.
I don't care what you do,
I want content that will ensure tipping.
Just like Wendy on the Trampoline,
that kind of video is like gold.
Don't shoot whatever you like.
What sort of video has high gold content?
Open your eyes and look around!
Wendy is the key to our fortune.
What do you have?
Pull the prank on her.
She already injured herself last time.
You're sure about this?
She's one of us and your diehard fan.
Let's think of something else.
That's the reality.
Whenever we run anything on Wendy,
the top-up rate is 50% more.
More than what you get
for both of your videos.
No, but you...
You have a problem?
OK, if Yat Wong Entertainment
has a problem with your video,
you better explain to Mr. Tsui.
Are we really going after Wendy?
This isn't the first time.
Wendy's known to be a goofball
and easy prey.
But this guy is heartless
to victimize a team member.
He's known to be a scumbag.
He's obviously jealous of us.
Our videos have higher hit rates than his.
That's why he pressured us
about the tipping.
He's so cheap.
Now that he's a KOL,
he's afraid we may surpass him.
Wait...why should we bother?
We have always shot and edited
our own videos,
let's just stick to our plan
and we'll get back at him with hit rates.
Good!
Let's fine tune our idea
and try to get more noise.
Wendy, we're shooting the Blind Gourmet,
if you give us the wrong answer,
the basin of water will pour on you. OK?
That's it?
The huge basin will have quite an impact.
Will Jarvis approve of this?
That's fine.
You're all covered up!
Is this a children's program?
I agree.
See? Even the model is complaining.
You need to do some introspection.
Put this on...
Instant hit.
It's practically see-through.
Jarvis, the basin of water is just
warming up.
The best is yet to come.
We saved the big punishment for later.
I want noise from start to finish.
Or else who'd want to watch?
No one till top up.
Wendy, you know what I mean?
Right! You want impact.
I'll change into that later.
Go get ready.
Right!
Peter!
You won't manage. I'll do it myself.
What is it, Auntie Ching?
Am I in your way?
No, go ahead.
I'm just being nosy.
Are you really going to wear
what Jarvis gave you?
It won't be just that.
I'll wear something else.
Still!
For you to wear something like that
in front of the camera...
You don't mind?
To get more traffic for the channel
and I can get more exposure.
If Jarvis thinks using me has an impact,
I must help him out.
You're very young,
naturally, you'd want to do your best.
But Jarvis often carries something too far.
Not to mention you hurt yourself last time.
Jarvis has vision.
He knows what's best for Little J Media.
Just remember, at the right moment,
you must protect yourself.
I know what I'm doing.
Don't ask me. Ask Modem and Peter.
They're behind the camera.
Wendy, don't tell me
you're wearing that underneath.
Just put this on.
That's no different from being naked.
Relax! We'll use forced perspective
when we shoot.
Stop standing there! Go change!
Mr. Tsui!
Jarvis, can you take a break?
We need to talk.
We're about to do a livestreaming.
Let me do this first.
Stop the livestreaming. We need to talk now.
In my room.
Ngai Ka-yan, get in here.
Well? Shall we go ahead?
Mr. Tsui is the boss. Pack up and change.
Tom, you look so smug.
Did you ask Mr. Tsui to drop by?
Tom, I didn't expect you to come to me
behind Jarvis' back.
You know Little J is a subsidiary of
Yat Wong,
and I give Jarvis a free rein of
what to shoot.
But Jarvis is getting out of hand
just to get noise.
He didn't care Wendy was hurt
and insisted we use her again.
I can no longer put up with it.
That's why I came to you.
From a business perspective,
Jarvis is making money for the company
and advertisers trust him.
To put it nicely, I'm in charge of Little J.
But Jarvis actually calls the shots.
Hegemony is not exactly healthy
for the company.
Perhaps, I can be useful to you.
Jarvis, what are you doing?
We don't want anything cheap.
If we have no viewers, we have no money.
Use your head!
I finished editing.
Let me know if you have a problem.
Are you in a hurry? Watch it with me.
(J Weekly)
(Correct Ways to Use a Wheelchair)
I'm helping you...
Are you OK?
Thanks.
Get up...
Thank you.
Come on...
What's wrong with you?
You're a wimp, pal. Have you eaten?
You can walk?
Who says I can't?
You played me for a fool!
Look over there, big guy!
Over here...
Hello, you're on J Weekly...
I can't believe after working
with me for so long,
the end product is so raw.
Yes, it's raw but viewers love this stuff.
The simplest and most direct way
to make people laugh
is considered a hit.
I'm curious...
remember what I taught you
about the objective of these pranks?
The nature of laughing is misfortune.
We laugh when we see
the misfortune of others.
You said you like to shoot these pranks
because if the misfortune of someone
is only known to one person,
then it's truly unfortunate.
But if we can record it
and make other people laugh,
sharing the laughter is considered a merit.
We should not waste a good laugh.
You still remember?
There's no need to imitate me.
Viewers' tastes have changed.
They want to see something exciting
and sensational.
I agree we need to adjust to
the viewers' tastes,
but I stick to my bottomline,
of nobody getting hurt.
You're right.
You're beginning to have your own thinking.
OK...here's your chance.
If this piece really worked,
I won't interfere with any ideas
you and Paul come up with anymore.
Don't look so shocked.
I'm telling you now,
I'll let you run your own channel.
Great!
It takes so long to load 20%?
We're dead if we can't upload it today.
Something wrong with the connection?
Connection is fine.
Maybe it's the network in the building.
I need to check.
Crap! We must go on air today.
What's the problem?
We have something to upload,
but there's a problem with the network.
Not something you can fix quickly?
OK, I need you both to attend a meeting
with me at HQ.
We need to upload it, you promised...
I'm good for my word.
Relax! If you can't upload it today,
do it tomorrow.
Let Modem take care of the technical stuff.
I need you for something big. Let's go!
I'm helping you...
When was this uploaded?
The sooner the better.
We have a lot of likes.
People are topping-up too.
Let me check...
What's wrong with you?
You're a wimp, pal. Have you eaten?
Wait...there are a lot of dislikes!
You can walk?
How come?
A host shouldn't talk like that.
That's cruel!
Wait...I only told him to smile
for the camera.
What did I say?
The nature of laughing is misfortune.
We laugh when we see
the misfortune of others.
If the misfortune of someone
is only known to one person,
then it's truly unfortunate.
But if we can record it
and make other people laugh,
sharing the laughter is considered a merit.
We should not waste a good laugh.
Who added this?
You didn't? Then who did?
There's only one possibility.
Speak up! Did you mess with my video?
I'm just doing my job.
I must follow the Boss' order.
Ngai Ka-yan, you set me up?
What are you talking about?
Quit your act! You recorded what I said
the other day.
You told them to edit it into my video.
Remember what I taught you
about the objective of these pranks?
You claimed to let me run a new channel.
That was just the bait to set me up.
What are you talking about?
Why would I do that?
Because you're jealous.
You're scared we would surpass you
and replace you.
That's why you're desperate.
Replace me? You and what army?
If I'm jealous of talents,
I wouldn't pick up garbage like you
and teach you to shoot and edit videos
and brainstorm.
Now that you can stand on your own feet,
you begin to challenge my ideas
and went to Mr. Tsui behind my back.
I did not.
No?
Then why would Mr. Tsui drop by
and stop my livestreaming?
You think you're good enough,
I gave you the green light to take charge.
And what happened?
Look at all the dislikes!
That proves you're both useless.
You admit you removed the original video?
Bloody hell...
Calm down...
It's Mr. Tsui. Did you call him?
Hello?
Jarvis, a representative from the Rehab Club
called and complained about
the wheelchair video.
Meet me at the Rehab Club.
OK, I'll be right there.
Look what you did, losers!
We have a complaint from the Rehab Club.
Now I need to defend you.
You're coming with me.
Clean up your own mess.
Hello, I'm Lok Hiu-sin, the representative
of the Rehab Club.
I'll cut to the chase.
J Weekly posted a video called
"Correct Ways to Use a Wheelchair",
I received a lot of input from members
claiming the video has
seriously affected them.
I'm sorry this has affected
your organization.
I'd like you to meet our colleagues
Jarvis, Tom and Paul.
They're in charge of this video.
Please let them explain.
Miss Lok, I created J Weekly.
I'm duty bound but it was my fault
I didn't supervise my colleagues properly
and created such inappropriate content.
I will remove the video immediately.
I trust my colleagues did not mean
to offend the physically challenged.
The video was only meant to be entertaining.
I know. You think your pranks are funny.
Because nothing unfortunate happened to you.
But did you realize,
the way you toy with other people's sympathy
when we truly need help,
no one will help us?
Tom, you said the nature of laughing
is misfortune,
if the misfortune is only known
to one person,
then it's truly unfortunate.
But if we can record it and send it out
so more people can see and share it,
then it'll be a hit.
Tell me, taking pleasure in our pain,
is that right?
Miss Lok, the voice over...
Tom, don't bother to explain.
This time you have gone too far.
Miss Lok, about the impact of this video
on your organization and the
physically challenged,
I would like to apologize on behalf
of Little J Media.
I also have a solution to make up
for our mistake.
We'll do a fundraising for the Rehab Club.
We'll apologize in public for the video
and do something for your organization
through the fundraising.
You're good with these pranks.
You know anything about fundraising?
You have nothing to worry about.
Pulling pranks is only one of our means.
Entertainment is what attracts our viewers
but it's usually lacking in
most fundraising events.
You're quite right.
I hope our collaboration
will be beneficial to both parties.
Jarvis, since the fundraising is your idea,
I'm putting you in charge.
I understand.
I will keep an eye on everything
and won't let Mr. Tsui or Miss Lok down.
Are you celebrating tonight?
Probably.
The Rehab Club is a big organization.
You'll get a lot of perks.
Let's not get into that.
Charity work is not about perks.
I'll come up with a brilliant idea
and try to raise as much money as possible.
(A few days later)
Folks, you're all participating in
a new project.
Tom and Paul are working on Tricky Ball.
Tricky Ball is suspended indefinitely.
We need to control our costs
and aim for producing high quality content.
(Static Apnea Challenge)
A Static Apnea Challenge?
Jarvis, that's amazing!
You have a new idea already.
This will take place underwater.
We'll invite other media to help us
promote the event.
It'll be on a much bigger scale?
It's nothing but a gimmick.
What's the challenge?
Will it be too dangerous to stay
underwater for so long?
We'll get a cylinder of oxygen ready.
Breathe in pure oxygen before
getting in the water
should be able to stay there longer.
I'll go get ready.
No need. You should have heard me
the other day.
It wasn't easy to make the Rehab Club
come around
and agree to let us handle
this fundraising event
to make up for your screw up.
The pair of you must take it upon yourself
to ensure nothing will go wrong.
Wait...you want us to buy the oxygen?
Is it that simple?
Are we getting any advertising money?
If not, get some wrapping paper
and wrap up the cylinder.
Anything else you want us to buy?
A weight belt,
to counter the buoyancy and
fix the underwater position.
Any other questions?
Is this purely a fundraiser? No pranks?
What do you think?
No fundraising events included any pranks.
I want to be the first.
But first, we must decide
who should go underwater.
I'm OK!
No, Wendy. You can't swim.
I already have an idea who it should be.
Are you kidding? Me?
Exactly! You know why?
One, you're a great swimmer.
Don't let your talents go to waste.
Two, in a way, this is your screw up.
I have done everything I could to help you.
Don't tell me you won't pull your
weight to fix it.
(Little J Media)
(Yat Wong Entertainment)
Don't look so glum, Tom!
I'm trying to figure out the prank.
He wanted me in the water,
but won't tell us about the prank.
I pissed him off before,
he's definitely trying to get back at me.
Don't worry! You know you're dead.
I know that.
But before I die, there's a jerk
I need to kill first.
Who?
You're probably the biggest jerk I know.
Don't think you helped...
No...clam down...
Take your pants off...I'll race you
I don't remove a guy's pants...
You were the champ in school...
Hi!
May I help you?
I'm looking for Mr. Ngai.
Jarvis, what am I doing for the fundraising?
Pull a prank on me?
Or let me host the show?
I can do it.
You want to be the host?
Daisy!
I knew we'd meet again soon.
I confirmed with Miss Lok
you're livestreaming the fundraiser.
I want a quick word with you.
You have time for an interview?
For you? Anytime.
Wendy, get us some tea.
Thank you.
Sit down.
Stop staring.
This chick has the looks and the body.
It's best if she's your girlfriend, right?
Don't get any ideas.
She's probably Jarvis' girl, pervert!
Oh dear, don't use cold water for tea!
Let me help you.
Thank you.
Can you take that to Jarvis?
I remember you said
nobody really understands you,
that's why you put on a mask to
pull pranks on people.
Can you elaborate on that?
Let me ask you a question.
To become a comedian,
do you think it takes countless tragedies?
Why are you asking me this?
Come in!
Auntie Ching, just put them down.
No reason.
I want to tell you the answer is no.
I simply enjoy the pleasure of
pulling a prank on someone.
So you made up a story and lied to me.
When people trust you very much
and you tell them you lied and
toyed with them,
they would have the same look
just like you right now.
What do you think, Daisy?
Jarvis, I have something to show you.
Can't you see I'm busy? Get out!
Hello, Miss Tai! I'm Tom.
I'm so happy to see you.
I watch your videos all the time.
You're prettier in person.
If there's nothing else, get out.
There is...and it's a good thing.
When I saw Miss Tai just now,
an idea popped into my head.
We can package the fundraiser better
by inviting Miss Tai to host it.
Me? I have never done it before. Can I?
You are articulate and have quick reflexes.
Livestreaming is a piece of cake.
You can definitely do it.
What's the key?
You have your audience base from NNL
and J Weekly has a lot of fans.
Bringing together the fans of
two platforms,
with Jarvis' planning,
I'm sure it'll increase the traffic
of both channels.
You're not exactly wrong.
Daisy, are you up for the challenge?
I never back away from a challenge.
You're not worried it's a prank on you?
No. You may not succeed either.
Folks, for the Static Apnea Challenge,
we have invited Daisy to join us.
What did you say in his office, pervert?
Why would Daisy agree to do
the Static Apnea Challenge?
Daisy claimed to come here for an interview.
Obviously, she's using Chief J to get ahead.
Didn't you see how Chief J lust after her?
He'll volunteer to go underwater
and I'll be off the hook.
He'll do it? Are you sure?
(Substitute for a Day Series - Waitress)
Your coffee.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Iced coffee for me.
Of all the NNL videos,
the Substitute for a Day Series
is my favorite.
You personally took on the challenge
and tried out the pleasure and pain
of different jobs.
I think it's very meaningful.
Thank you.
Didn't you invite me over today
to discuss the fundraiser?
Where's Jarvis?
Jarvis will be back shortly.
We can start without him.
I've been thinking
how we can better package our collaboration.
Why don't we add elements of
Substitute for a Day?
You worked for a massage parlor before?
You wish to position me as the masseuse
to give you a massage after
the Static Apnea Challenge?
When I finished holding my breath
underwater for 20 minutes,
you'll take over as the substitute masseuse.
That's the perfect integration.
I want to know how is it different
from ordinary massage.
You mind giving me a demonstration?
OK!
Oh...that's so comfortable.
You're really good at this.
What are you doing?
Tsang Chun-kit, what's wrong with you?
Why did you ask Daisy to meet you?
No wonder you volunteered to be the host.
Because you found a way a satisfy
your lust, you pervert!
Me? It's for the good of
the livestreaming.
I want to add elements of the
Substitute for a Day Series,
in order to get the greatest synergy.
Spare me your excuses.
I won't let you do it.
Daisy and I had this sorted out.
If you pull the plug now,
people would think this is child's play.
That's not for you to worry.
I'll do the Static Apnea Challenge myself.
You just take care of the rest.
OK!
Is everything OK?
All taken care of.
Chief J is not only a scumbag,
but also a lecher.
He said I'm doing this
to satisfy my lust,
he should speak for himself.
Then we're all set.
Good show, baby!
Just put it on the table.
What's this? When did you rent this place?
Never mind that now.
Chief J pulled enough pranks on others,
it's time we turn the table on him.
Tom, what are you going to do?
Leave that to me.
He's taking on the challenge,
I'll swap his oxygen cylinder with
a stink bomb.
After he inhales from it,
he'll cough like he has tuberculosis
and make a fool of himself
and become the laughing stock.
This plan is perfect.
Except for one flaw.
What?
You know how to make a stink bomb?
I got everything ready.
I'm counting on this baby.
Does it have to stink so bad?
Chief J put us in charge of the oxygen,
we'll give him a special edition
of 20 cylinders.
Great! But will he fall for it?
He already put on half of his wetsuit.
Better count again, 1...2...3...4...
What's that?
Oxygen cylinders for the
Static Apnea Challenge.
You're taking them to the storeroom?
Yes.
Wendy is in there looking for something.
It's a mess. Just leave them over there.
OK. Let me just run to the toilet.
Where's the gas for the starter horn?
Somewhere in here. Start looking.
They never put anything back
and leave things lying around.
What are you doing?
I'm trying to see if it works.
That's the oxygen for the
Static Apnea Challenge.
Then where's the gas?
Right here...
Can you not be such a slob?
Keep an eye on it, pal.
I will, pal.
(The day of the incident)
(J Weekly x The Rehab Club
Charity Fundraiser)
Hey, is everything ready?
Almost.
Daisy, can you step over here?
Jarvis will soon go underwater
for the Static Apnea Challenge.
Like we discussed before,
if he meets the target of
staying underwater for 20 minutes,
you'll give him a massage, OK?
Any questions?
Nope. I can't wait to see your prank.
There's a table over there,
with a case of pure oxygen cylinders on it.
Can you get one for me?
Stop hitting on the girl.
Where's the weight belt?
I'll go get it.
Is this the one?
Didn't you bring them over?
Yes!
Hello, everyone!
The livestreaming of J Weekly
and the Rehab Club's
charity fundraising Static
Apnea Challenge will now begin.
We're honored to have Daisy
from NNL Production as our guest host today.
Thanks for the invite from J Weekly.
I'm happy to be part of the livestreaming
of this meaningful fundraiser.
We hope to raise the public's awareness of
caring for the physically challenged.
Daisy has another role today.
After our challenger holds his breath
underwater for 20 minutes,
Daisy will become a substitute masseuse
and give him a sports massage.
You can't wait, right?
Without further ado,
let's turn to today's challenger Jarvis,
the person in charge of J Weekly.
Thank you, Daisy.
I'm honored to work with the Rehab Club
on this charity fundraising event.
Too bad Miss Lok of the Rehab Club
can't join us today
but it won't affect our incredible show.
Are you ready?
Yeah...
Let's hear it...
Come on...
Jarvis is ready to inhale pure oxygen,
and the Static Apnea Challenge
will soon begin.
I wonder what prank Jarvis will pull today.
I don't know.
What's going on?
What did you give him?
I know...Jarvis is toying with us...
So, this is the prank?
Ngai Ka-yan, what an act!
You can quit now and get up...
Jarvis...
He's not breathing...Jarvis...
Get up, Jarvis...
Is everything OK?
Jarvis...
Are you OK? You're scaring us!
Wake up...
Wake up! Stop it...
Jarvis...
How is he?
Get up...
(Three months later)
Ngai Ka-yan was dead? Just like that?
How bizarre!
We found out Tom and Paul meant to
pull a prank on him
and give him a stink bomb.
But we never disclosed this to the public.
J Weekly had an Static Apnea
Challenge before,
they meant to use one of these
to trick one of their own.
But these kids mentioned this
on their video.
Something is fishy.
I searched Agent J Channel's IP address.
It should be in this building.
Their base is here? Go find them.
We got something. Cut him off.
Police! Freeze!
Stop running!
Stay where you are!
Looking for me?
Over here.
Gogo Sir, right?
Say something, Sir!
You're on live...I'll give you a close up...
Hey...
Watch it! Don't break anything!
That's personal property.
Want to make an arrest?
How many cuffs do you have?
Arrest me, Sir!
Go ahead and arrest me...